good morning this feeling one second I'm
just gonna go post a link on Twitter so
that anyone watching there can come and
join in however all I'm seeing is me in
my unicorn onesie from yesterday there
we go takes a whole second together
alright and even write that yes I should
have a copy pasted no people can know
it's just a link how do you know what
what is the purpose of the link unless
you're watching to come join and I can
put it on here as well although you
can't sadly click on it I wish she could
alright let's see so I was sitting here
making notes for possible danger in the
pandemic and this question was coming up
the one that I put is the title how
responsible are we for one another
because well not because I think we all
have a different amount of this one's
for later one another some of us feel it
more strongly and some of us feel it
more weakly but our actual duty is
probably the same I don't I feel
responsible for all of humanity and
creating a world that works for everyone
so clearly that people over abundance of
responsibility I think this pandemic is
showing us how fragile our system is and
how interconnected we truly are that
like how even if you're only in it for
yourself even if you're acting with a
hundred percent selfishness how much
Duty do you have to other people in
order to maximize your duty to yourself
if other people don't have health care
and they have communicable diseases
that's going to cost you if other people
are in poverty and that means they're
making life choices that are gonna be
impact you financially because you know
they break into your car to get the last
three bucks in there because they don't
have money because they have addictions
because they have
how much do we actually owe one another
I am looking at this as an opportunity
the Pens I make that is hopefully we are
able to come together and solve our
collective problems together instead of
leaving it up to each individual to
solve them that is a big problem of what
we're currently doing and I command that
person from stream yard I so having a
world that works for everyone doesn't
mean you have to negate your needs or
desires in order to placate to everybody
else but it does mean if you are looking
at your your highest life generally
involves helping other people live their
highest life if any percentage of
humanity is able to tap into a tiny bit
of their genius and purpose and a tiny
bit of their connection to other human
beings that matter to them tiny bit of
their purpose and a tiny bit more of
what they need to actually accomplish
that then we can do it all rather easily
but if we stick to our normal current
silos of well you're in it for you I
meant for me I've got to solve it for me
I've got to figure out put roof on my
table roof on my table for eating roof
tonight he'll figure out how to put a
roof over my head and food on the table
then we're gonna get the world we've
always had and worse because our
economic system actually doesn't know
how to come back from this a cooperative
economic system does and is actually
emerging during the pandemic we can see
that people are choosing to give their
gifts for free if they're able to if
they have the financial capacity to do
that even a lot of times when they don't
have the financial capacity to do that I
know that in Canada people are
are able to get up to like $2,000 a
month right now during the pandemic see
if I can get I oh joy joy you're having
a bad life today how are you doing
during the pandemic since I can't ban
you why are you so I don't even saying
gree why are you so hurt I mean I don't
understand we do in fact thank goodness
have some Jewish people oh baby here we
didn't and during these times of crisis
a lot of people use their you to lash
out at absolutely anybody and and put it
on someone else another group of people
it's definitely not what it's about to
to be responsible for other people they
ruined your young time you mean your
childhood oh I don't know what that
means but who didn't have their
childhood ruined when you're an adult
it's time to figure out what you're here
to do what can you do to benefit
yourself and other people
whatever your people are clearly you're
not including those people I don't know
what they what they did but it's I don't
an entire group of people can't do
something to you so it can't be them who
did it even if a few of them did I mean
right now virus is holding the human
race hostage it's in no way evil it's a
virus it has biology what did describe
against you look like I mean the
knee-jerk reaction honestly the one I
would have bugs on periscope is to ban
you for what you said would you first
came in but there's some reason you're
here today there's some reason that you
clicked on this scope of how responsible
are we for one another and are staying
here and commenting so what is it that
was an organized discrimination guessing
you mean an organization that
discriminated against you and an
organization made up of those people but
that again doesn't mean all of those
people got together and decided that you
were someone they could discriminate
against there are clear organizations
who've done a lot of evil in this world
and it still isn't all of them the
Catholic Church for one has done a lot
of evil in this world still does a lot
of people in this world but that doesn't
mean every Catholic person is doing evil
they're not responsible for everything
the Pope does even though they kind of
choose their religion they choose if
they're Catholic or Protestant I mean to
the point he wanted to study engineering
and math your mouth was good but they
wasted your life for an English test so
your entire life problems drill down to
one English test that got failed that
sucks I mean it sucks to to be really
good at one thing and not be able to do
it because society needs an overarching
bar of like well your English has to be
this good you're you're writing and
reading skills have to be this good when
honestly you could probably excel at
math and science without that even if
science and math wouldn't let you excel
at that without it so you went to
university and we're a top student that
doesn't sound like they they destroyed
your life that doesn't that sounds like
you went to university of where top
students like you
your power up to people from your past
as if you let that be the language like
they ruined your life or what is the
language you use screaming it against
you they ruined your young time people
go through some hard and that is
partly what we are here to overcome is
how do you pass on less of that to the
next person the next generation steps
not by group eunuch people together
making them evil but if that's what
you're current inside Malthus all you do
they rejected your application for a
higher degrees despite having good marks
right which every post-secondary
institution does to everybody all of the
time they you know you can get this is
our part of why post-secondary
institutions are broken face is that
they need people they only allow they
only admit people who have top grades in
every subject which means people who
would excel at one particular subject
and kind of suck at other ones aren't
gonna be able to do their life but that
society but society it happens to
everyone and happens not to everyone
because if you're good at all the
subjects then you get in and if you're
not good at all the subjects then you
either have to figure out how to get
good at those particular ones or you pay
the price and that is partly what we are
fixing in society is how responsible are
we for one another because it's not just
your I don't believe that that language
that your life is ruined but even if it
was true that your life was ruined it's
not just your life that was ruined if
you're truly supposed to have been an
engineer I don't quite understand your
story because it sounds like they did
something that didn't allow you in but
you still went to university and got top
grades so I don't know how that's ruined
but assuming that it is that if you've
got in and out when life would have
worked in this house somehow this one it
didn't we are not getting your best self
I mean clearly you the anger and the
frustration that you feel towards that
group of people you're not
to show up is your best self not in this
scope and not in the world and so we
don't get you we don't get you as a
mathematician or an engineer but it's
not really them who did that I mean if
you're not letting yourself show up as a
mathematician engineer there are tons of
people in the world who don't have
degrees which it sounds like you do and
they still work in their field because
it's their passion and purpose no-one
can kind of no one is a gatekeeper to
your passion and purpose and that
includes if you're a medical student if
you're someone who wants to heal and be
a doctor and you cannot get into med
school because there's gatekeepers you
still can find a way to live that
purpose and passion into the world
without being a doctor you are talented
and they wasted your time you wasted
your time I mean how can someone else
waste your time if there didn't let you
in they were the kekeke gatekeeper for
whatever institution that was you you
went somewhere else and you got it you
got your degree yeah that sucks
again they everyone's gonna pay the
price for that if they're being against
you because of your race and therefore
you didn't get to get into that school
and therefore you don't think you got to
show up in the world in the right way
why would they like if everyone who
wanted in that school got in that school
irregardless how do you know it was
based on your race and not based on who
you are you can't ever I mean just like
when I go out in the world I can't know
if something's discriminating against me
cuz I'm a woman or queer or because
they've had a bad day you can only kind
of look at it you'd have to see their
statistics how many people if they let
me go apply it every people they let in
vote for their grades well then why
would you wanted to go with them like
people who reject you in whatever
capacity for a relationship your family
a job are doing you a favor if they
don't like you why would you want to be
with them
okay I don't
just said you went to university and got
you mean you got a degree and then they
wouldn't let you into post-secondary
because he didn't have English she
didn't get your master's degree or your
PhD see a story doesn't lie make sense
in that one he wanted to have a higher
degree what would have happened if you
had a higher degree what would be in
place right now that isn't in place you
know maybe you're on our worlds as
racist as fuk like classist and ableist
and it is what it is right now until we
make it better you would feel better but
you're letting this anger and this
hatred towards this group of people who
you think hurt your life that is the
thing you're holding on to and that is
the thing that it's wrecking your life
they're not thinking about you they
don't give a they don't know who
you are they don't remember this how
many of yours down the road you're
holding on to it how was your talent
wasted do what you want to do go what is
it you would be doing right now if you
had gotten into that institution and
everything had gone according to plan
nothing would have gone according to
plan it all would have fallen apart
anyway but what would what do you think
like would have been like them and why
aren't you living that it's not really
on other people
you were the best student in university
at math and science courses at your
university but when you apply to a
post-secondary you're in with all the
other people sorry post post-secondary
that doesn't work we've apply for
post-grad courses programs that's part
of the word you're in with all the top
top students for your PhD like there's
this guy out in Squamish who studies
bears and he does not have a biology
degree and when I was getting my a
biology degree my dad was working there
at the library I went out to watch him
and he is amazing because this is his
passion he doesn't care if he has a
degree he goes out and he studies bears
and he's come up with this ingenious way
with that biologist because they didn't
learn it in school don't do of like
weighing the Bears getting their
collection of their hairs they go under
a barbed wire - it collects them and and
has cameras and he has all of these
things that he does that now people
employ a decade two decades later but he
was one of the first people doing it he
didn't have a degree and honestly he
might never be known in that field
because he doesn't it's not like the
biology um
world is going to accept if he writes a
paper he doesn't have a degree they
won't they won't let it but he's still
learning about bears he's still doing
his thing what is it that is in your
dream that doesn't require other people
to give you the okay what is it you're
here to do I'm here I'm saving the world
I'm like figuring out how to get this
fantasy world in my head that works for
absolutely everyone out in the world
there's no there's tons of gatekeepers
for that but no one can really stop
being except for me nobody can because
I've tried and I've tried to find them
convinced me that this isn't isn't the
the solution because no one can find a
hole that can't be filled like working
together to create solutions finding out
how we can come together with our
emotional issues with everything and
still we're
work in our own self-interest and have
it be for the collective good helps
everyone but if you need everyone's not
be how they currently are it's not gonna
work I don't need people to not be on
the edge where they are you had problems
applying for jobs too you loved it your
father's place well that's pretty lucky
I mean you have parents you can live
with that that is a possibility
doesn't it honestly doesn't matter where
you are in life
any place you are there's gonna be
people who are way better off than you
and people who are way less off than you
and you can focus on and you truly can
pick which one to focus on what if
you're gonna compare yourself to someone
which one are you gonna compare yourself
to I would suggest not comparing
yourself to anyone and just finding what
makes you happy how can you find beauty
and joy from exactly where you are what
brings joy to your life you can't go
back in time and get a degree then you
could get a PhD now yeah I mean in
Canada once you hit 65 you can go back
and get and get degrees for free that
makes me upset in the whole other level
but hey you can there's there's other
options there's tons of things you can
learn on line for free master classes
and YouTube channels it didn't exist
probably at that time period
why have you been unemployed I'm
unemployed but I have health conditions
student loans I don't who pays for your
rent and food right now you can do
generally speaking if phd's a little bit
different but generally you kind of get
paid to do HD you don't get paid welds
do it but you get paid a little bit OCD
and anxiety so your item I don't
understand you're unemployed so you're
not working so someone's paying your
food and rent you have time to study an
OCD and anxiety as somebody with anxiety
I don't have really OCD it's for my
autism you don't live there you mean
where you wanted to do your PhD you can
do distance learning this mean you're
gonna get in doesn't mean especially
with the current current attitude but I
mean you know any of us he's gonna let
you in when you come in talk to you like
that these groups of people that wrote a
lot of hate speech against are hurting
me let me end because because you owe me
you owe me to let me in what are you
offering them what do you have to give
to the world if you're able to be happy
and live your live your dream it's not
worthless first of all all degrees are
useless all of them but it's whether the
person who's hiring you has value in
them
so if somebody finds value in in who you
are and what you have to give they will
depending on the area hire you
regardless whether you have the distance
won or not but if you want to take the
education for you because you want to
have that information
then it doesn't matter if it's distance
but sitting in your father's basement
feeling bad that other people didn't let
you get into a PhD problem program I'm
guessing a decade or two ago
isn't doing you any favors no one's
gonna come knock on your door and be
like I'm sorry the world was mean to you
here get into this ph.d program this
might be harsh you've achieved exactly
what you deserve because those people I
can even give you that they were
absolutely racist horrible to you even
though I have no idea who they are or
what the circumstances were but even
then the universe gave you exactly what
you were supposed to get exactly so the
fact that you got anger and bitter about
that and didn't find another avenue and
didn't that's your current lesson what
are you learning from it how can you
move forward from that right it might
reject your application a million times
it was at the same university again and
again and again again well twice a few
times we'll go three he projected your
application right because people can
reject your application people have been
like you can't save the world so many so
many including my loving loving badly
right so then you start your own
institution and reject people you can't
oppose the degree you start the
institution to do that but feel like
you're better than other people is a
coping mechanism to be okay that
somebody rejected you does it make it
true and it also doesn't make it in any
way true that you're less good than they
are okay
they very well I'm again giving you the
benefit that they were absolutely how do
you know you're smarter than them cuz
you got better grades in math and
science you're the top University
doesn't matter
that doesn't make you smarter than
somebody else
I got top grades in my high school
doesn't mean I'm smarter than other
people in fact if you think other people
are stupid
it generally means you are if you can't
find intelligence and beauty in every
human being it's because it's a
reflection of what you feel about
yourself so if you're looking at the
world we've seen them as stupid for
having rejected you there's something
that that's there to teach you again
they're not thinking about you two
decades later they don't know who you
are just another person they rejected it
from from their list and you're right
there might be absolutely racist people
constantly hire people and get let
people into programs that look like them
without consciously thinking about it oh
you remind me of myself when I was
younger of course you're in oh look
another white guy cuz I'm a white guy in
power and then your uncle it's just like
baby me that is the way Society
currently is and works unless we come
together and figure out how to make a
better way there isn't going to be a
better way so the next generation is
gonna go through exactly what you went
through like I don't know if those
people are racist but I can tell you you
are huh who's the one who said racist
stuff in here I don't know whether they
did it or not they probably weren't
using racial slurs when they were
talking to you
there's subconscious bias might have not
let you into the program but it sounds
like your English wasn't good up to
their standard so that is the metric of
you getting into their institution if
you didn't meet that metric
who's why would they let you in and not
somebody else who had as good of grades
in math and science if that is the thing
you were going into for PhD and had good
ink had decent reading right
skills higher right Radian writing
skills well it's not useless for
engineering because you need to
communicate with people but I'm not most
post-secondary institutions are pretty
useless like that you need to make to be
as someone who's had to deal with a lot
of doctors
I really wish they had a different
entrance to medical school because a ton
of people who never will get into
medical school would have made much
better doctors and the doctors that are
there because they've had OCD and
anxiety they've dealt with having having
cancer in high school with those very
people are never going to get into
medical school and they would be much
better doctors to patients but they're
not going to because the medical school
isn't gonna let them in I can't I don't
get a say in that not right now
yeah but they go change the institution
that people shouldn't be even English
degree but they do what they started
they don't shouldn't have to be able to
read and write at a university level in
order to be able to do math from science
at a university level
I've had a university degree in science
and it was ridiculous the amounts the
the amount but science students had to
learn the arts at a university level but
the opposite was not true the aid the
art students who had to take math and
science took baby math and science i sat
in on one of their classes it was like
volcanoes erupted looks like I'm sorry
why are we studying Shakespeare with all
the other Arts students at their level
and there's like baby science classes
for they for the art students explain
this to me
why aren't why don't they have to take
calculus why don't they have to take
university level math and science class
it's like we have to take university
level English classes but that is what
it is so you either change it or you can
be bitter your whole life that it's not
there or you can accept what you've
actually been given and make the best
part of it
yes I can see you can read night that
doesn't mean you have it at a university
level I am a geneticist by trade I took
at University and I was the best
genetics student in the class by far I
helped at least four or five people get
A's in that class when it came time to
write the the final I got sixty in it
because I read the test to be way more
complex than it was
I answered questions at a higher level
than what it was but they marked it at
what it actually was of course and so I
got 60% and wasn't like me like I went
in was like this can't be
I couldn't possibly have gotten this I
did I got 60% of my genetics test even
though everyone I helped got 90% on it
that didn't mean I was less good at
genetics because I got 60% and it also
didn't mean that I that he should give
me a 99 because I was the smartest in
class he was the smartest in class and
knew how to how to answer the questions
that other people didn't and I got 60%
the final this place like have been
simultaneously and the opposite could be
true there are tons of people who are
amazing at getting good grades and
horrible in the workforce like horrible
and actually being on a team you might
have been one of them sounds like maybe
you don't you not a big team player and
it doesn't really matter what degree you
get if you can't work with other people
I mean a lot of engineers aren't team
players but at the same time what do you
then do they need you to have that basic
level before you get in you didn't you
didn't get in what is it about
engineering that you really wanted to do
dude everyone was bullied at school
everyone and if you weren't like you had
like you have other lessons to learn
you see new people you don't feel safe
yeah that's I mean it's what the world
has proven to you time to time again
right that new people aren't safe but
then when you meet new people
and you treat them as unsafe you're the
one who's acting unsafe if you go back
and read the comments on this scope
I wasn't being unsafe you were being
unsafe this is not an invitation for
friendship and and dialogue that you
that you that you handed out I have
dealt with my my bullying my my
health struggle is that I can I can and
I don't have the power to get you out
that this is exactly how this is
supposed to go I know this is this is
how the universe unfold so I take every
lesson it gives me with gratitude and
that's a bit of a stretch I take every
lesson and eventually get to God it's
you about it Walter all accounts fake
you're not you're right but where are
you for friendship my point isn't that
you came here looking for friendship
it's that this is how you treat people
online of course you're gonna get
and bio back the universe proved it to
me again people are mean they're unsafe
you came in here spouting things about
the Jews like really but you don't avoid
people online there's something or seek
you know there's something whether its
attention or a place to put your anxiety
you're seeking out something I mean I
had this conversation a few months ago
on camera with this guy who had been
convicted strong word alleged when he
was it called me you think someone's
done a crime anyway people said that he
can't he had he had raged them and he
was now showing up in this in this new
space it was just a weird like it was it
was weird how the conversation came
about but there was something about over
I was like I'm supposed to reach out to
this guy and have a conversation and
while we had this conversation it was
one of the best conversations I've had
the last three or four months now how to
make
seeking conversations in the last three
to four months because there was
something about him and his shadow side
that showed me my light in a whole new
way like I was like yeah I thought
should happen to be but quite frankly
the universe shows up for me in a very
real beautiful way when I'm open to it
and the opposite had happened to him and
so he had the worldview of like well you
know I'm isolated right now but the
neighbors are gonna hate me in a few
years then I'll have to move because
that happens constantly like well that's
the pattern here live you know so so
yeah that is gonna happen but and I
don't think he could even comprehend the
gift he gave me in that in that
conversation I don't think you know the
gift you're giving in this conversation
there is no negative like there just
isn't and we all show up how we're
currently capable of it this is your
best self in the moment I can I can deal
with anyone's about self in the moment
even though it doesn't look like
anyone's best huh like this doesn't look
like anyone's version of their best self
but today right now I get it you feel
better since the time that you stopped
believing in God I don't think I do no
no I don't I miss the time when I was a
kid or I could just like give things up
to God just pray on it but I feel more
authentically II having given up God but
when I talk about God I don't mean that
God
I definitely don't mean the God from the
Bible I don't think that God whatever
they are can be seen from the outside
can only be seen internally so it's only
something that can prove itself to you
it's not about proving it to everyone
else the God the the God the capital G
God that judges everything and gives me
Ten Commandments some of who make sense
and some of them don't
yeah I don't believe in that God but I
do believe in whatever this magical God
that is not a god thing that shows up in
my life is and gives me everything I'm
supposed to have it exactly the right
time including my bowl
including every conflict that I've had
in the last well ever but definitely the
last few years because there's more to
learn from conflict than there is from
kumbaya Ness the brain changes then
you'll be able to find the right word at
the right time all of it all of it's
exactly what it's supposed to be what do
you believe in what makes you feel good
I mean a lot of people aren't gonna come
wealthy we live in a new world right now
and there are a ton of people who make
money who are not white they probably
don't have your attitude and probably
don't go in places talking like like
that because that would never even if
they feel it on the inside it's not
coming out and they probably don't feel
it on the inside cuz people can feel
that resonated but even if they do if
they're actually races then I mean the
white world is not gonna feel that and
they can get ahead the world is unfair
you want all people to have a house and
live house to live and food to eat me to
that's what I'm actually doing in the
world you don't need a degree to do that
you don't need anything to do that you
just we need enough people to come
together and live their best selves
you're a communist so what are you doing
to make that dream a reality what are
you doing to actually make sure everyone
gets something else to live in and food
to you well you're not gonna get an army
no one's getting an army you if you
can't recruit one person talking to
myself you definitely can't recruit ten
thousand or a thousand or a hundred but
what can you actually what can you
actually do from where you are because
if you're good at
in science even if you don't have an
engineering degree you can do it your so
you can DIY tiny houses create
permaculture create actual food for
people how do you promote communism
because nothing you've done so far is
already communism in any kind of a
positive light anyway like I mean I'm
basically an anarchist communist so I'm
not that hard to convince you know all
I've been talking about is how for the
last three years it's how we can
dismantle capitalism and create a world
that works for everyone using fake
accounts how's that working going closer
to communism because I don't I don't
think we we have I mean I have this
conversation with a few Bernie bros as
well as some Christians whatever your
ideas actually are whatever your ideals
are I mean I don't know maybe you're
absolutely not a communist since you're
interacting you know like a racist so
that you turn people off of communism
because that is what you're actually
doing but if you are truly a socialist
or a communist and you want people to
follow those ideas or you're a Christian
you're a vegan or hear Bernie bro
whatever you happen to be if you're
putting it if you are a representation
of your beliefs and values are you
showcasing them as positive and people
want to be drawn to that or you
showcasing them as negative and how
responsible are you for that if you turn
somebody off of Jesus if you turn
somebody off of veganism if you turn
somebody off of Bernie or communism
because of your attitude and how you
showed up in the world you're doing the
opposite of what you actually want to be
doing it's probably better to not talk
about it at all until you can be a pot
like a beacon for it
I know Christians in my life and I have
wounds with that church who are
absolutely beautiful human beings who
make me be like oh I don't want to be
like if I'm still Church because because
they're good friends like good human
beings who appear happy and they don't
constantly tell me that I need to go to
church don't have by saving my soul
saved by deaf
don't think Bernie's a fraud I don't
know what what do you think is is it
about him that makes him a fraud - you
mean I honestly think of you as like a
Bernie and Steve fraud I mean you could
have other issues of Bernie but if you
look at him and see fraud it's mirror I
don't know what's a lunch earned
donations by acting as a communist his
track record like he's Bernie back in
the sixties it's not like he just got no
bandwagon for queer rights and social
equality and like he's he's been touting
it the whole time and yeah he accepted
donations how do you not accept
donations and he just dropped out of the
race because he didn't want people
during the Pens I Mike to have to feel
obligated to give him donations you need
necessarily know the gain in this race
there was a long time it looked like
Bernie was the front-runner and he did a
lot by running they'll push the agenda a
little more left but honestly I don't I
don't care about who's the Prime
Minister of Canada I don't think leaving
it up to the big them is solution I've
been coming together and figuring it out
ourselves is the it's a better place to
be yeah but he's only he's only doing it
so that Trump does get elected no one
should support Biden he's almost as bad
as Trump but it's one of two options and
I'd rather Biden and Trump barely we're
just like I said you yeah you did like I
didn't say you get what you deserve I
would never say that but you you're
creating the life you're currently
living we're all doing that on a grand
scale - we created cope at 19 we created
the political system ran we created the
fragility we currently see by leaving it
up to the Bing them by not coming
together and figure you know and you
know I'm Jewish ancestry but I'm not
Jewish
I do not identify since I have no none
of the cultural and it's my dad's dad
who's Jewish not my mom's mom but I mean
I see anti-semitism is about the biggest
call for helping the bastard as you
possibly can because I don't even know
what to say about it like anti-semitism
is ridiculous on so many levels but it's
like a place to put your hatred and
anger and so I see it as a hateful angry
person who's hurting not as someone
who's mistreating my hands history cuz
yeah just doesn't Bill Maher is an
atheist and he's Jewish
I get it you can be both yeah it's
Jewish I'm not an atheist I can't save
any theists after everything I believe
but I don't believe in the Christian God
I celebrate Christmas cuz it's fun but
Judaism is is a both a culture and a
religion you can be one without the
other and you can be like me who has the
genetics and is no way like I could
emigrate to Israel because I'm one
Jewish grandparents dad so I've one
Jewish grandparent so I could I could
theoretically but there's a whole other
whole issue with that I'm not okay that
I can immigrate there people live there
for generations can't vote but no when I
don't care - I mean honestly that
there's like an elite group of people
that are that are doing anything in the
world I don't think we're smart enough I
don't think we're connected enough and I
don't like that they could ITT to be a
conspiracy theory I'm like do you see
how inept all our politicians are at
this this is the worst conspiracy ever
they're all flying by this
they're pants they're all like oh my god
what do we know the economy uh-huh it's
bad conspiracy theory same with all the
world leaders getting together and
deciding on anything no there are some
things that happen behind closed doors
and people definitely do things for for
money and for profit and for power and
privilege but I don't think there's a
lot of you don't even need them to be in
cahoots about it
people working in their own
self-interest for profit yes all right
we don't hear about their own good time
I'm so conspiracy theorists well I'm
shocked which is the issue with
basically all of it is that you never
know whether someone is a good or bad
actor like I mean half the hashtags on
Twitter are designed by Russian BOTS and
then people are like yelling at each
other that this thing's had that this
thing is trending it is what it is it's
like right how do you know it's trending
for real reasons honey on there's actual
people behind it and then people like
you go out and whether you're actually
racist or not you're racist because even
pepped it's worse if you're not racist
and you're out in the world acting
racist because it's a it's a fake
account trolling people and if you're
getting paid for it it's actually even
worse there are a lot of Jewish people
in media and everywhere just like
there's also a lot of
which isn't any conspiracy it's because
Jewish people look white and were racist
as fuk conspiracy says solved
[Music]
there is no how responsible are we for
one another I'm just gonna go back to
that you can t we could see no kitty
nobody pays you can't even consistently
stick to a story
you're the worst conspiracy theorist
you're not as good as the other ones but
even but there's people I trust online
I've had conversations with them on
camera you can usually get generally a
fairly good feel for them and but I've
some of them anyway I have yet to meet
in person I don't think I require
meeting them in person if I found out
they were paid by some Russian
organization to mislead game B I
wouldn't be shocked I would be shocked
and that for them is individuals I
wouldn't be shocked for the overall
thing to happen sounds like a stellar
human being
you exist in the world so I'm willing to
make a world that works for you by which
I mean a world where you can live from
your highest genius and purpose clearly
not one where you get a world without
white people and other such I'm say
minorities wait I just blank it well
awesome I don't know what to tell you
about that like you are an adult living
with your parents and you still aren't
treating them well I never the ones do
not to kick you out they're the ones who
have to help you figure out that you're
you've got your own but so much makes
sense yeah this one might be the real
one that you come from a rich family and
you're entitled it's but wait you
come from a rich family they're racist
against you the race is because you
can't don't have money because like none
of your makes sense buddy you need
to let go into acting classes and really
like rehearse your backs for B you can't
that's love it
none of it makes sense who's gonna pay
for my room and board when I do my ph.d
program your Rich Dad you know the
racist against thee and only Jewish
people are rich oh wait my dad's rich
it's your dad Jewish are you wait
well then he won't like that's a bigger
problem than some Rando strangers not
letting you into a degree program based
on an arbitrary bureaucracy that's like
right you didn't have them English
grades to get in you didn't check that
box you didn't get in your dad not
paying for your school I'd have a bigger
problem with him but if you put your
anger and hatred on that then you can't
really live with him can you you're
getting more from him than he's costing
you but you're giving up your power you
can move out and figure it out on your
own
tons of people don't have rich parents
and are no way able to rely on them you
might do better if
if it's coming with other strings
attached I mean yeah clearly or spoiled
in every in every regard I mean can we
read all your comments and see that I
was bullied yeah so was everybody they
didn't love me on University and oh my
life is ruined ruined forever
that is rich people problems rich people
problems like well my daddy didn't pay
the Alumni to lemmya and you've ruined
his life around paying for your studies
yeah sounds like something good in
generational drama just to full
disclosure after this I'm going on
periscope and probably bad news you
don't come into a Futuroscope but this
is the day that you were supposed to
come in and do this so I mean you're
welcome to of course going on to any of
your other fake accounts I'll just be
doing it much faster next time so I
realized right although I don't have I
can't bound people on here I can ban
people on here yes I authorized it well
wouldn't I authorize it it's me post
that - they're like the same app doesn't
matter ok what's going on writing them
in for authorizations interests
if I want to look at finding some
friends but you don't need people but
everybody needs people and everybody is
worthy of connection it's finding who
you're supposed to be connected to I
avoid people all the time I have
socially oh I can't even say I have
social anxiety I had social anxiety I'm
still avoid you might like great I love
all of my friends I'm like I can't talk
to the one video chat right now because
I'm so overly extended with like these
our chats in the mornings for other
things and then my kid that I'm like oh
ho I have too many people like I have my
introvert to me has enough connection
that I can't do anything else even
though I love the people and I really
want to connect with them like after the
pandemic I don't know you enjoy talking
to random strangers I mean hey there's
things coming down the pipeline for
everyone to be able to do that however
you won't be able to have a fake account
what if you can't have a fake account to
talk to random strangers what if you
actually have to show up as yourself on
video or voice I'm 44 zero but I mean
really that's just the number of times
if it rounds done I'm both
simultaneously a teenager yeah he's an
80 year old so I've in no way actually
for you we're good at making fake
accounts how do you be good at making
fake accounts you just make fake
accounts you mean in the new system only
matter who you are and you show us so
you could tell me anything I'm a doctor
and this actually actually I'm an
engineer actually I let people into
engineering programs none of it makes is
real none of it matters because one I
can't affect to Kate know if it's real
and two it just actually doesn't matter
it doesn't matter to me who you actually
are it matters to you that what we
create together and I don't mean you and
I mean just the world the society in
general that we don't allow people to
have fake
it's because this is what they show up
as they show up as racist misogynistic
assholes who are like but I'm not like
this in real life it's just a part of
play it's just like the worldly tumor
they don't they need you to show up as
your authentic self including if your
authentic self this racist misogynistic
then show up that's that but you don't
need to show up as a fake version of
that to pretend to be that so that it
somehow helps the world but if you like
fake accounts aren't actually helping
anyone they're not helping you they're
definitely they're not other actually
helping me the whole universe is exists
help me and you and everybody but you
don't take what seriously life your life
your purpose your passion
I mean I'd live it from a place of like
divine humor everything is pretty pretty
freaking hilarious but note laughs we
could cry so it's laughs and everything
but helping me to stay at home stay at
home all the time this is my life
this is my normal so it's not really go
help someone else stay at home everyone
stayed at home just fine you're not like
this isn't a conversation I'm what I'm
gonna look back on in a month and
remember so it's not having that big of
an impact like the other one where I was
at least on video with the guy and he
was he had there was a lot going on with
that one I could see him as a real human
being who was had a lot of happen
to him and you might be that too but I
need like you're a rich spoiled kid
being a troll you're someone who feels
bad and somehow some white people are
racist and let you into an engineering
program despite the fact your daddy's
French and couldn't like your daddy
didn't pay to let you in I don't really
understand your conflict but again you
need to rehearse your backstory have a
fake account but have an actual persona
with it so that you can follow along
it's harder to stay and to keep up with
lies than it is to keep up with the
truth
but the world does it like if you want
to be a bad guy go do role-playing go
literally be a bad guy in something
we're inviting you to do that you know a
bad guy on the Internet is actually
making you a bad guy you're not helping
anybody by doing this you're not helping
yourself you're still lonely you're not
fine actual real connection and when
people don't like you like see people
don't like me people are mean and people
do like you or they're trying to help
you you're like I don't need anyone like
I hope you actually do have friends in
real life but this is the kind of thing
people do and then they wonder why the
world is against them because you are
against the world even in virtual
reality you could show up as a saint
you can hit someone if it shows up it is
like helps everybody with their problems
why do you choose this as your persona
an anti-semitic and anti white person
who feels bad I mean again I would have
blocked you this and but like how is
that fun how is that fun cuz again if I
was on periscope and not on stream yard
I would've blocked you at the first part
the first comment cuz he never would
have had any of this conversation how is
that fun I don't understand I'm you know
I'm literally never been blocked by
anyone I don't get it but it gives you
your adrenaline rush or it gives you
some sense of validation that you're
important enough that somebody blocked
you when really it's basically you're a
mosquito
thanks a limb I come on every morning at
8:30 vandana and Jeffrey will not be
back but I will be every day it's
talking about this conversation oh I can
do it now since you like it wait till
the next one bill you could disturb them
so it gives you a sense of power that
you disturb them hmm I
still don't I mean why do I be that
person in the world yeah that's great
that you could chew dude you didn't
guess I was a Jewish you asked and I
said I have some Jewish ancestor this
person do this after well my lack of
tech skills I can't do it right this
second but no creating a world that
works for everyone listening to your
actual inner guidance is magic I mean
this is magic in its own way because
everything in the universe is showing up
exactly how it's supposed to including
you but I don't think you're getting the
best you out of this I again I'm not
gonna remember this conversation in a
month I have a much better conversation
going on down throat at 1:00 p.m. where
I get to talk to somebody about his life
world-changing idea which is my thing I
really enjoy doing that you do worse
things to great it says like the
Internet has given us this weird sense
no because we're both like humans are
very trolli online yet I've never had
I've had people call in to periscope
when I'm actually on periscope itself
and they'll be assholes for the flight
they'll say something stupid or racist
or gross in like the first 30 seconds
but if they actually talk for 5 to 10
minutes they will never just like chime
in and say that then it's like we
only troll in the begin like we only
troll when we can hide behind a keyboard
and we're not our voice we're who we
can't attach to the human being and we
do that all the time and then we've read
someone's words and we read something
into it respond in that way I mean I
have a ton of video chats with people
this is what I'm on the planet to do at
the moment and nobody shows up it's a
troll people show up is not their best
self they have emotional issues they
have personality conflicts but nobody
shows up as a troll just like it
Thanksgiving dinner you might have a
racist misogynistic uncle but he's still
kind of doing the best he can and he
generally doesn't try to piss you off
it's just his giving right he's just
what he does he's not trying to do that
but like trolls online I just like I
don't understand the validation I
understand wanting to play a bad guy on
TV I understand wanting to like find
that part of yourself why like why
spread misinformation why spent if
spread anger and fear and hatred because
it's not it's just gonna come back at
you and it's like then everyone's
trolling everyone's like oh cuz it's my
persona I can put off online it's not
giving anything and then you can't feel
good at the end of the day despite what
you're saying about it feels good to be
banned by people does it actually in a
moment it might but overall it can't it
can't feel good to be like boom I did my
work today I was bad but I have people
how happens he'll feel good I don't
understand but luckily when we create
the social media where we can't have a
million fake accounts and we show up on
video chat as our real authentic selves
and we can get real connection and see
who people really actually are and then
there's Hylian and beauty that happens
there that can't happen in text they
can't happen with people trolling but
there will always be trolls so having
people with one authentic account helps
that in a lot of ways we can all hurt
people more than more than we do I could
go out and stab somebody I'm not going
to because there's no fiber of my being
that wants to do that but we all could
hurt more people we can also do beauty
and love in the world you choose which
wolf to feed nobody else canning
nobody's gonna pay as high a price but
unless they're murdering other people
besides view even murder and other
people you're probably gonna pay the
higher price for that karma and hell in
whatever comes after this but also just
in this life we don't feel good when
that happens I mean of course they can
anyone can be a troll on the internet it
does not make you special and unique you
make you
whatever you actually have to give
that's not behind a fake persona about
it because if you're giving your fake
self there's nothing there to love and
attach to there's nothing there that's
real so even if everyone loved you right
even if you were weren't a troll and you
were the opposite you're charismatic but
that's not your true self and people
like you they're not liking the real you
if people hate you because you're
trollee and they're not that kind of
hating let me know you because you're
choosing to show up like that this is
well it's not me in real life yeah it is
this is real life you're wanting to have
an impact on other people that hurt them
where they block you you can't have that
power over me nobody has that power over
me all that have and have wielded that
power have been severed from my life
yeah that's I mean is that a proud thing
is that something that makes you feel
good that you abused your family I know
I'm Staffie with my kid and my dad and
doesn't make me feel good not like that
was a successful conversation I made him
feel bad like why do I show up like a
teenager like a party
my my I have to go cuz it's been an hour
but my advice to you would be like sit
with your
stop going online and sit meditate sit
with your own stop putting
everything on everyone else your dad the
others sit with it it's the only way
you're gonna ever get to happiness enjoy
it's sitting with the anger and the
grief and the sense of not being enough
because you wouldn't be on trolling
people in a negative way can you tell
people in a positive or negative way
unless you weren't okay with you I can't
be okay with you whether you show up as
a good or bad person you're not even a
you to my percent in my consciousness
you're not even really human being
because you're just burns on it on a
screen I get that you are a real human
being whoever you are
it's choosing to type things but I don't
have a say in who you are I don't know
who you are I don't know which part is
true which part isn't true
all I can know is myself and what
I'm giving to the world it's true and
what lessons I get from all of the
people and events and things that happen
in my life they should die because they
are old well they're probably not
leaving you their money
so is that why you want them to die I'm
very clear anyway it's been a minute
it's pretty year spin it
those died periods it's been an hour I'm
gonna go like to say it was nice
chatting with you bad Jenna but it was a
day it was an hour thanks for helping me
fill the hour I'm here every hour I will
not be seeing you again with this
persona so it was nice chatting with you
if you want to come in with a decent
persona maybe even your real one you
were welcome back